go2mobi.com 2014-06-25

# Go2mobi - Mobile Advertising | Mobile RTB - RTB Privacy Policy

### RTB Privacy Policy

Go2mobi is a dedicated Mobile Demand Side Platform (DSP). We help agencies and advertisers to plan, execute, evaluate and optimize their mobile advertising campaigns via our platform (the ‘Platform’). This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with information on our privacy and data protection policies as they pertain to our Platform, and website, located at www.go2mobi.com, (our ‘Website’).

If you are looking for the privacy policy for the ads you may have seen on another website or smartphone application you can view the privacy policy for the Go2mobi RTB [here](http://go2mobi.com/privacyrtb.php).

What types of data do we collect via the Platform?  
We don’t collect Personally Identifiable Information via the Platform. PII is information that may be used to identify you personally. We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (‘Non-PII’) via the Platform. Non-PII is information that can’t be used by Go2mobi to uniquely identify you. The Non-PII we collect includes but is not limited to the date and time of your mobile browsing and mobile app usage activity, mobile apps used, the pages viewed, browser type, general location such as zip code, your mobile carrier, network connection type (e.g., 3G vs 4G), your device identification number (e.g., UDID, mac address), device type, make and model. We also may obtain demographic data (e.g., age range, gender and estimated purchasing power) to enhance the capabilities of the Platform. In certain cases, we may obtain the precise location of your device and we take reasonable precautions to ensure that your permission is obtained for the use of such information.  
Go2mobi uses cookies (on mobile devices where they are enabled) and similar technologies to help store a Go2mobi ID and other Non-PII and to help us record user expressed privacy choices. We do not use zombie cookies or other mechanisms that may circumvent your privacy choices.  
How do we use the data collected via the Platform?  
We use the information collected via the Platform to help make our clients’ advertising messages, more relevant and interesting to you and more effective for our clients. This helps pay for free websites and apps out there, many of which would not be able to operate without the ad revenues. In some instances, we combine this information with other Non-PII obtained from third parties in order to enhance the features of our Platform. We share the aggregated, non-individual specific, data we hold with clients, publishers (mobile sites and apps) and other third-parties for ad delivery, reporting, accounting and other legitimate business purposes. In these cases we work with organizations we believe to have appropriate safeguards in place to protect data at the levels we require.  
In situations where we are obligated by law, we may also disclose information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, included but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Go2mobi may disclose your information when obligated to do so by law and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected, or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. We reserve the right to disclose aggregated, non-personally identifiable information collected to third parties for any purpose.  
Finally, Go2mobi may transfer information, including any personally identifiable information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change. If Go2mobi is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your PII, as well as any choices you may have regarding your PII.  
What are my opt-out choices?  
If you’d like to opt out from having Go2mobi collect your information for ad targeting via our Platform, please [click here](http://www.go2mobi.com/terms.php). When you opt out, Go2mobi will note your device ID as having opt-ed out in the database on our servers. Once flagged as having opted out, Go2mobi removes the Non-PII attached to your device ID from our database, and will no longer target ads to your interests. We record your opt-out choice via cookies or HTML5 depending on the operating system of your device. Please note that if you delete, block, or otherwise restrict cookies or HTML5, or if you use a mobile device or browser, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.  
Go2mobi recognizes the importance of providing notice in as many different places as possible to help ensure that consumers understand their privacy choices. Thus, we are experimenting with providing an enhanced notice; located on many of the advertisements that we serve via the Platform.  
How long do you retain information collected via the Platform?  
Go2mobi generally retains information on the Platform no longer than six months. However, our retention policy is geared to the level of sensitivity of the data collected. For example, to the extent we obtain precise location information, we only store that information for up to 30 days, and then roll that data up into non-precise segments (e.g., postal code, or metro area) and stored for up to six months. Mobile identifiers are stored for up to six months, after which it is irrecoverable deleted. Whilst stored, the UDID is encoded using either MD5 or SHA1 algorithms, which makes it impossible for us to find the real and original UDID. We may store de-identified data for up to two years, and aggregate data for up to five years.  
What types of data do we collect via the Website and how is it used?  
The Website is directed primarily to businesses. We generally collect PII such as name, postal address, email address and phone number when it is provided to us. Where we receive requests for information, direct emails or other communications, we will generally use such information to address your specific question or facilitate your specific request. We also collect Non-PII such as your IP address and browser type to help us properly administer the Website.  
Do you collect information about children?  
Our Website and Platform are not directed at or developed for persons under the age of 18. Go2mobi does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If the company is made aware that it has received personally identifiable information from someone under 13, it will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from its records.  
What are your data security policies?  
Go2mobi has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All the data we hold is protected by multiple layers of physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, to secure it against accidental, unauthorized or unlawful access, use, modification, disclosure, loss or destruction. No method of transmission over the mobile web or method of electronic storage is 100% secure; therefore, while Go2mobi strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee absolute security.  
How are changes to your privacy practices communicated?  
This privacy policy is subject to change. If Go2mobi plans to make any substantive changes in the way we use the personally identifiable information under our control, we will post a clear and conspicuous notice on the website and in this privacy policy prior to the changes being made – and as appropriate, we will also let you know about the choices available to you regarding such changes here.  
Need further information?  
If you have any questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, please email or mail us:  
email: info@go2mobi.com  
address: Go2mobi Inc. 5-774 Bay St, Victoria, BC, Canada, V8T5E4
